ccp.edu 2017-10-05

# Privacy Statement | Community College of Philadelphia

## **Online Privacy Statement**

Community College of Philadelphia respects the privacy of all proprietary visitors to this website to the extent permitted by law. This online privacy statement is intended to inform you of the ways in which this website collects information, the uses to which that information will be put, and the ways in which we will protect any information you choose to provide us.

There are two types of information that this site may collect during your visit: website visit logs, and information voluntarily provided by you.

## **Web Visit Logs**

The Community College of Philadelphia website routinely collects and stores information from online visitors to help manage the site and improve service. This information includes the pages visited on the site, the date and time of the visit, the internet address (URL or IP address) of the referring site, the domain name and IP address from which the access occurred, the version of browser used, the capabilities of the browser, and search terms used on our search engines. This site makes no attempt to identify individual visitors from this information: any personally identifiable information is not released to external parties without your consent unless required by law.

## **Information Voluntarily Provided by You**

In the course of using this website, you may choose to provide us with information to help us serve your needs. For example, you may send us electronic mail through a web form to request information, you may sign up for a mailing list, or you may send us your address so we may send you material. Requests for information will be directed to the appropriate staff to respond to the request, and may be recorded to help us update our site to better respond to similar requests. We will not sell, exchange or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information without your consent, except to the extent required by law. We do reserve the right to work with third-party vendors, to host this information solely for the purposes intended by Community College of Philadelphia and in accordance with this policy. We do not retain the information longer than necessary for normal operations. Each web page requesting information discloses the purpose of that information. If you do not wish to have the information used in that manner, you are not required to provide it.

The Community College of Philadelphia website may provide links to other World Wide Web sites or resources. We do not control these sites and resources, do not endorse them, and are not responsible for their availability, content or delivery of services. In particular, external sites are not bound by the College's online privacy policy; they may have their own policies or none at all.
